atta.ai 2019-12-21

# atta

This " Privacy Policy of atta Co., Ltd." (hereinafter referred to as "This Policy") is stated as terms and conditions of using of Privacy Information (means information defined This Policy Article 3) acquired from users (hereinafter referred to as "User") of Services(hereinafter referred to as "The Service") which is operated by "the atta Co., Ltd." (hereinafter referred to as "the Company").

## Article 1. (General Provisions)

  1. The Company shall respect the privacy of User and manage Privacy Information manage Privacy Information thereof in a diligent manner.
  2. The Company shall manage and use Privacy Information in addition with laws and other regulations as "Business Operators Handling Personal Information" defined by "Act on the Protection of Personal Information" of Japan (hereinafter referred to as "the Law"). In addition, the Company shall manage and use Privacy Information collected from User who lives in EU that corresponds to "personal data" ,set forth in "General Data Protection Regulation（EU 2016/679）"(hereinafter referred to as "GDPR"), in accordance with GDPR.
  3. The Company shall continuously and permanently focus on establishment of company structure, education of employees, etc.
  4. User may provide Privacy Information voluntarily except when required. However, in case where User has not provided the information, the User may not take advantage of all or part of The Service.

## Article 2. (Agreement to This Policy, Withdrawal of Agreement)

  1. When User provides his/her Privacy Information to the Company, he/she is deemed to have read This Policy carefully and agreed with all provisions of This Policy.
  2. User may withdraw his/her agreement to using of Privacy Information by the Company at any time.
  3. The agreement and the withdrawal of his/her agreement of this Article shall be made by predetermined method specified by the Company.

## Article 3. (Privacy Information Collected by the Company)

  1. Privacy Information collected by the Company from User is as follows; 
    1. name, address, telephone number, mail address, and other information which corresponded "Personal Information" set forth in the Law;
    2. information related specifically to User other than Personal Information which corresponds to personal data set forth in GDPR,
    3. location information collected by using GPS,
    4. IP address, access log,
    5. Information of browser, etc. collected by using cookie, etc.
  2. The Company shall not collect "Individual Identification Codes" and "Sensitive Personal Information" set forth in the Law from User.

## Article 4. (Collecting of Privacy Information)

  1. The Company shall collect Privacy Information by legitimate methods, and not by illegal methods that is contrary to User's will.
  2. The Company shall notify or publish User of the purpose of use Privacy Information in advance.

## Article 5. (Purpose of Use of Privacy Information)

  1. The Company may use Privacy Information for the purpose of the following (hereinafter referred to as "Purpose of Use"). The Company shall not use Privacy Information for other purpose without acceptance from User in advance or being recognized by law. The Company may change and add Purpose of Use by changing of This Policy of Article 10, User shall agree it. 
    1. To give important notice to User for providing User with The Service.
    2. To send catalogue, present, or newsletter, etc. relating to The Service of the Company.
    3. To respond to an inquiry, etc. from User;
    4. To caution or warn against User who violates any terms of The Service, and to check against past disposal situation of him/her for such caution.
    5. To confirm identity of User when he/she requires disclosure, change, addition, deletion, etc. of his/her Registered Information.
    6. To improve The Service continually.
  2. The Company may create analysis data from Privacy Information collected from User and statistical data from the analysis data of multiple User. The Company shall pay attention not to include personally identifiable information in the data of previous section, and the Company may use these data without any limitation as long as the Company uses in a format that is impossible to identify the individual of User and to inquire for Personal Information.

## Article 6. (Provision of Personal Information to Third Party)

  1. The Company shall not disclose or offer Privacy Information to any third party without prior approval of User, except for the following. 
    1. In the case where the information has been disclosed or offered by a method incapable of identifying individual of User.
    2. In the case where such disclosure or offer has been permitted by the laws and/or regulations, or in the case where disclosure or offer has been required by public agency based upon the laws and/or regulations;
  2. In the case where the Company has delegated some or all of The Service to any third party to the extent necessary to achieve the "Purpose of Use of Personal Information" or in the case where the Company has transferred The Service because of transferring its business such as amalgamation or other reasons to any third party, the Company shall make arrangement with the third party about handling and managing of Privacy Information with same degree of diligence as prescribed in This Policy.

## Article 7. (Managing, Maintenance of the Accuracy, Retention Period of Privacy Information)

  1. The Company shall diligently manage Privacy Information provided or disclosed from User. In addition, in the case where the Company has disclosed the Privacy Information to employees, the Company shall limit the number of employees and make arrangement with the employees for maintaining confidentiality thereof.
  2. The Company shall make an effort to keep the Privacy Information accurate and latest, within the scope necessary for achieving the Purpose of Use. However, User shall be responsible for accuracy and freshness of Privacy Information and shall waive the company all the damages arising to the User from it.
  3. User shall waive the Company all the damages arising to the User from the following. 
    1. In the case where Privacy Information of User has been disclosed or divulged by the User.
    2. In the case where any third party has obtained Privacy Information by accessing to him/her account which is caused by an intentional act or a negligence of him/her.
  4. The Company shall take appropriate and necessary measure to prevent the Privacy Information from being leaked, lost or injured and to manage the Privacy Information safely.
  5. The Company shall store Privacy Information disclosed or provided from User for following period. 
    1. Privacy Information of User who sign up with The Service as Member: During the membership period and 3 years from the expiring day
    2. Privacy Information of Other User: 1 year from the day of disclosure or offer
    3. In the case where the Company has no longer needs to use Privacy Information stored by the Company, notwithstanding the previous section, the Company shall make an effort to delete the Privacy Information with no delay. The same shall apply in the case where User has required the Company to delete his/her Privacy Information.

## Article 8. (Claim to Inquiry, etc. by User)

  1. User may claim to inquiry, disclose, adjust, add, or delete his/her Privacy Information against the Company. In addition, User also may claim to suspend to use his/her Privacy Information against the Company.
  2. The claim offset forth in previous section shall be made by predetermined method specified by the Company. The claim shall be made only by User himself/herself, his/her legal representative (if User is a minor), or agent who is authorized by him/her regarding the claim.
  3. In the case where the Company has received the claim set forth in this Article, the Company shall confirm the User's identity and shall respond to the claim within a considerable period after the Company's confirming such. In the case where the Company has decided not to deal with the claim based on the law, the Company notifies him/her accordingly.
  4. User shall pay following fees to the Company at the time of the claim of disclosure, etc. 
    1. Fees for claim of disclosure and inquiry JPY700_ (includes postage fee)
    2. Fees for claim of adding, adjusting, and deleting For free

## Article 9. (Using of Analytical Tool, etc.)

  1. In order to improve The Service provided with User or for delivery of proper advertisement based on hobbies and preferences of User, the Company may collect the information about User's behavior history, etc. by using analytical tool such as Google Analytics™. In addition, the Company may post or display a part of advertisement on Website regarding to The Service by using behavioral targeting advertising system provided by third party provides and using cookie such as Google AdSense. Regarding Google Privacy Policy that apply on the services that Google offers such as Analytics, AdSense, Google Map API, see corresponding website such as below.   
<https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>
  2. User may refuse collection of his/her Privacy Information by the Company or hide the behavioral targeting advertising either by disabling cookies in his/her browser, or by opting out via the webpage associated with the analytical tool or the behavioral targeting advertising.
  3. User shall take self-responsibility for the change of setting, etc. of previous section, and User shall waive the Company all the damages arising from his/her change the setting, etc.

## Article 10. (Change of This Policy)

  1. The Company may modify This Policy by sole discretion of the Company. In the case where the Company has modified This Policy, except for the case of urgency, the Company shall notify such modification to User in advance by method that the Company considers appropriate.
  2. Modification of This Policy shall become effective immediately when the Company uploads the updated This Policy on the Website related to The Service.
  3. If User has not agreed with modified This Policy, he/she may claim to delete his/her Privacy Information against the Company by method set forth in Article 8.

## Article 11. (Measures at Leakage)

  1. If leakage of a part of Privacy Information stored by the Company has occurred, the Company shall notify accordingly to supervisory authorities with no delay and make an effort to solve the problem by complying with Laws, other regulations and instructions by the authorities.
  2. Even if leakage of a part of Privacy Information stored by the Company has occurred, unless otherwise stipulated by law, User shall waive the Company all the damages arising to the User from the result.

## Article 12. (Chief Administrator)

  1. The Company shall appoint the following person to be Chief Administrator of Personal Information, and try to manage Personal Information appropriately and to improve enforcement of policies relating to protection of Personal Information continuously. In addition, the following person shall be the contact point for inquiry or advisement about Personal Information and for the claim set forth in Article 8.  Operator of The Service | the atta Co., Ltd.  
---|---  
Desk for Inquiry | Personal Information Desk  
Address of Operator | 5F gran+NISHINIPPORI 5-6-10 Nishinippori, Arakawa-ku, Tokyo Japan 116-0013  
Phone Number | +81-3-4500-2185 (available in weekdays for 10:00-17:00 in JST)  
E-Mail Address | [privacy@atta.ai](mailto:privacy@atta.ai)  
Method of the claim for disclosure, etc. | by mail, by email  
  2. In the case where User has had an objection regarding to management and using Privacy Information by the Company, User may claim supervisory authorities.

Updated on 11st April, 2019  
Updated on 13rd March, 2019  
Updated on 15th July, 2018  
Established on 8th May, 2018
